http://blueribbondesigns.com/terms_shipping.html

0 items in bag
Subtotal:
Policies - Terms - Shipping - Privacy
We use cookies to better understand how the site is used and give you the best experience. By continuing to use this site, you consent to our Cookie Policy. Click to learn more
All Cookies
Default Cookies
PRICING:
All prices are as listed.
All prices are subject to change without notice.
All prices listed are in U.S. dollars (USD).
Kansas state residents are automatically charged 9.475% sales tax at checkout.
Canada and International customers, you are solely responsible for any customs charges, duties, VAT, or other taxes charged by your country.
All needlework designs include charts and instructions only, unless noted in the product description - all supplies (including fabric, threads, and finishing materials) will need to be purchased separately.
PAYMENT METHODS:
Payment methods include PayPal, Amazon Pay, and all major credit/debit cards. Please contact me before making a purchase, should you like to place an order with a credit card over the phone, mail me a check, or if you need to discuss an alternate payment option.
SHIPPING:
Shipping charges depend on the weight of your order, your shipping method, and your location. After entering your address information during the checkout procedure, you will see shipping options and pricing. I use USPS (United States Postal Service) and UPS (United Parcel Service). Contact me before ordering, should you prefer/require other shipment methods.
Electronic tracking information is provided for all envelopes and packages shipped to addresses located in the United States. International customers may need to select USPS Priority Mail to receive tracking information (and in some overseas areas, tracking information is not available).
I ship promptly. Items will generally ship in 1-2 business days with the exception of weekends and holidays.
Please use care when entering your shipping/payment information - I will not be held responsible if you enter your information incorrectly.
Once your package has left the building, I am unable to control the speed of delivery. Many times packages will arrive in Europe and other overseas destinations within a week to ten days; however, packages can also take quite a bit longer (3 weeks or more).
RETURNS POLICY:
At Blue Ribbon Designs, we strive to exceed all of your expectations. Should there happen to be a problem with your order, please contact me within 3 days of receipt and we will work together to rectify the situation.
Requesting a cancellation: a cancellation request must be recieved before the item/package has shipped - we cannot retrieve a package once it has been picked up by the post.
Due to copyright restriction, printed materials, charts, and patterns cannot be returned.
Electronic charts/patterns (PDFs, eGoods) are non-refundable.
COPYRIGHT INFORMATION:
All of the patterns/charts/designs on this website are owned by Belinda Karls-Nace and Blue Ribbon Designs, Copyrights 2004 through 2020. All Blue Ribbon Designs cross stitch, needlework, sewing, and quilting patterns/charts/designs and the Stitch Starter Ruler are protected by the United States and international copyright laws. All rights are reserved. Blue Ribbon Designs (including, but not limited to: patterns, charts, graphs, designs, instructions, directions, diagrams, images) may not be copied, scanned, uploaded, digitized, and/or posted on the Internet without written permission. If you have questions regarding my copyright policies or see Blue Ribbon Designs charts illegally uploaded to the internet or being "shared" in web based groups, please contact me using the "Contact Us" form.
You may not reproduce, copy, or redistribute the design or layout of this web site, individual elements of the web site design, or Blue Ribbon Designs images, designs, adaptations, charts, instructions, or logos without the express written permission of Blue Ribbon Designs, LLC.
PRIVACY POLICY:
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or opt in to our newsletter. When ordering, registering on our site, or signing up for our newsletter, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, and/or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).To process transactions and print shipping labels:Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic newsletter emails, only if you opt in to receive our newsletter. Only those who request a subscription to our e-mail newsletter will be subscribed.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'My Account' page.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at:https://blueribbondesigns.com/terms-and-conditions.html.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on 04/10/20.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
https://blueribbondesigns.comBlue Ribbon Designs, LLC18515 W 194th TerSpring Hill, KS 66083-4562United Statesdesigner@blueribbondesigns.com
© 2004 - 2020 Blue Ribbon Designs. All rights reserved.
